

Dorđe Vasić

Front-End Developer

Contact

Phone

+381 60 546 0943

+381 63 821 8306

E-mail

vasicdjordje@hotmail.com

Skills & Languages

PHP

Advanced

JavaScript/React

Advanced

SQI / GraphQL

Advanced

HTML5/CSS3

Expert

Adobe Photoshop

Advanced

English

Advanced

Reference

axios.ba lagalica.net karatesavez.rs.ba fenixmma.com fenixmma.com/blopen Experienced Web developer and Graphic Designer with 13+ years experience designing, drawing, and programing. Talented freelancer with wide aspect of work that can do when it comes to developing and designing. Involved and individualy finished many projects with great variations in demands (from simple websites, e-commerce, wordpress, custom aplications to corporate applications and games). Excelent team player and successful sportsman ready for improvement and learning every day.

Experience

2006-10- Graphic and Web design

2019-12 Freelancer

- Developing responsive Web application and websites depending on users choice end use.
- Using HTML, CSS, jQuery and PHP code that stores user input into MySQL Databases and delivers it to the end users.
- Creating application with corporate administrative UI.
- Creating Wordpress websites and e-shops Woocommerce websites
- Expirience working with MySQL, designing database structure
- Designing UI/ UX
- Experience using codding patterns and version control tools
- Linux and Windows Server configuration
- Creating custom PSD and HTML templates and shifting existing HTML templates
- Using JavaScript in developing different kind of tasks
- Using NetBeans and Atom IDE tools
- Basic SEO

2010-06- **IT Business analyst - Expert Associate Postal tehnology Engeneer** 2019-09 *Poste Srpske A.D. Banja Luka*

- Complete monitoring of software development the SDLC and participating in its construction in all its stages using Agile software development.
- Detailed analysis of the manufacturing and technological processes of the Company and the creation of documented proposals for business and technical solutions (BRD / FSD).

Education

2017-2018

ITAcademy, Belgrade Web Developer

2000-2007

Faculty of Technical Sciences, Novi Sad

MASTER of Postal traffic and telecommunications

Tehnical capability and competence

Technologies:

PHP, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, Apache

Coding patterns and CMS Systems:

React.js, Gatsby, GraphQL, Yii2, JQuery, Angular, Bootstrap, Wordpress, Joomla.

Designing Software:

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, InVision Studio, Corel Draw, Adobe Premiere, Dreamweaver.

Version control:

Git - GitHub

Other Software:

Microsoft Office Suite, MySQL Workbranch

Hobbies:

Karate master, Brazilian jiu-jitsu brown belt, coach and active competitor